http://www.rkfrantz.com/privacy/

RK Frantz Software, Inc. Privacy Policy
RK Frantz Software, Inc. values your privacy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy,
please direct them to privacy@rkfrantz.com and we will respond by email within 2 business days.
Information Collection and Use
Our Site uses forms in which you give us contact information (including your name, address, telephone number, and
email address) so you can place orders, request information and support, and make product suggestions. For certain services, we
may also request a credit card number or other financial information. We will then create an account number for you.
We receive and store any information you enter on our Site or give us in any other way, including through email, telephone,
or other communications with our customer service department. If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal
record of what support was given.
We use your information to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our Site, and to notify you of
account billing information, including sending a copy of invoices of products and services you order.
We use information gathered about you from our Site statistics (for example, your IP address) to help diagnose
problems with our server, and to administer our Site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us
improve our Site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally
identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.
Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and receipts. We use cookies to identify you
so you don't need to log in each time you visit our Site. The cookies are linked to your customer number, which is associated
with the information in your account.
This Site also contains links to other websites. Unfortunately, RK Frantx Software is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.
Security
This Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information
under our control. Please view our Secure Ordering page for further details.
Updating Your Information
You may alter your account information or opt out of receiving communications from us at any time by signing
into your account control panel and following the links provided.
Sending Emails
We use emails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested.
We also provide email links, as on our "Contact Us" page, to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to promptly reply to your messages.
The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this Site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded.
Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement
We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any
information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to
respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights, to protect the safety of the public
or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to
comply with ICANN's rules, regulations and policies.
What Happens to my Personal Information if I Terminate my Account?
When your account is cancelled (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is
placed in "deactivated" status on our relevant internal databases. However, deactivation of your account does not mean your personally identifiable
information has been deleted from our database entirely. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information if necessary in order to comply
with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.
Changes in Our Practices
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to
this Privacy Policy and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances,
if any, we disclose it.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:
RK Frantz Software, Inc.
839 Royalwood Ln
Oviedo, FL 32765
Rev. 03/10/2010       Copyright © 1994-2010 RK Frantz Software, Inc. All rights reserved.
Copyright 2009, 2011 RK Frantz Software, Inc. All Rights Reserved. This site may
not be copied, in whole or in part, without prios written permission from
RK Frantz Software, Inc.
